MARVIN JOHN AGBUYA

FRONT END DEVELOPER





EMAIL marvinjohnagbuya@gmail.com



LINKEDIN linkedin.com/in/marvinja

Developer and Designer specialising in fields such as UX/UI, Front End Web Development and Game Design. I've worked as a Microsite Developer at Serviceseeking.com for 7 months, an Assistant Administrator at Hajos, Anstee & Associates for 1 year and I have been working as a Website Administrator at ICMS Australasia for over 2 years.

SKILLS

<u>HTML5 CSS Javascript Sass Bootstrap p5.js Git Jekyll Gatsby.js JSON</u> <u>PHP Node.js</u>

<u>UX Design</u> <u>Web Design</u> <u>Game Design</u> <u>Wireframing</u> <u>Agile Methodologies</u>

Microsoft Office Affinity Designer Affinity Publisher Affinity Photo Mailchimp

EDUCATION

2013 - 15

BACHELOR OF DESIGN COMPUTING

University of Sydney

2016 - 17

ADV. DIPL. OF PROF. GAME DEV. - GAME DESIGN & PRODUCTION

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

REFERENCES

Contact details available on request

Web Master

BLAIR HARDAKER

ICMS Australasia Pty Ltd

Executive Director

SUELLEN HOLLAND

ICMS Australasia Pty Ltd

MARVIN JOHN AGBUYA

FRONT END DEVELOPER





EMAIL marvinjohnagbuya@gmail.com



LINKEDIN linkedin.com/in/marvinja

EXPERIENCE

2018 - CURRENT

WEBSITE ADMINISTRATOR

ICMS Australasia Pty Ltd

Responsiblities:

- Created and designed websites for conferences from briefs given by clients
- Used HTML5, Sass, CSS, PHP and Bootstrap, Javascript, Jekyll, Gatsby.js to create websites and emails
- Updated websites and created new features such as: Event Programs, Speaker Biography Modals, Image Galleries, etc.
- Create emails on Mailchimp for each conference
- Corresponding with Event Managers
- Use Affinity Designer/Photo to edit images to be suitable for the web

2017 - 18

ASSISTANT ADMINISTRATOR

Hajos Anstee & Associates

Responsiblities:

- Created manila folders for new clients
- File organisation
- Digitisation of Corporate Registers
- External client organisation
- Data Entry

2013 - 14

MICROWEBSITE DEVELOPER

Service Seeking Pty Ltd

Responsiblities:

- Edited HTML, CSS, Javascript files to create microsites.
- Attached Google Analytics to the microsites
- Updated main website with links to the microsites.

MARVIN JOHN AGBUYA

FRONT END DEVELOPER





EMAIL marvinjohnagbuya@gmail.com



LINKEDIN linkedin.com/in/marvinja

VOLUNTEERING

2016

QA TESTER

Epiphany Games Pty Ltd

Responsiblities:

- Tested games for bugs
- Discovered how the bugs occurred and how to reproduce them
- Reported Bugs using JIRA

2013 - 16

GENERAL EXECUTIVE AND DANCE TEACHER

Soulxpress Hip Hip Society

Responsiblities:

- Taught hip hop/urban choreography classes
- Organised and choreographed performances for events
- Helped other executives with tasks to help organise events and gatherings